CHERYL CAITANO

CONTACT

P.O. Box 1651, Kamuela, HI 96743

(808) 640-4416

cheryl.caitano@gmail.com

EDUCATION

FUNDAMENTALS OF SYSTEMS ENGINEERING CERTIFICATE

California Institute of Technology 2014

B.S. IN MATHEMATICS (MINOR IN PHYSICS AND ASTRONOMY)

Western Washington University 2007 — 2012

SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Bookkeeping
- Collaboration
- Communication
- Customer Service
- Data Analysis
- Leadership
- Multi-Tasking
- Persistence
- Problem Solving
- Process Automation
- Project Management
- Software Proficiency
- Time Management

PROFILE

Excellent technical, organizational, and time management skills used to streamline processes/procedures and enhance employee productivity and profitability in both small business and large corporation environments. Proven project management, troubleshooting, and team collaboration experience. Strong computer abilities and able to learn quickly and efficiently. Highly adaptable and reliable, requiring minimal guidance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OFFICE MANAGER

Horizon Automotive, LLC/Kamuela, HI / 2015 - Present

- Receive customers, schedule appointments, delegate technician work statements, and organize/maintain efficient virtual and physical filing systems. Document all processes and procedures. Maintain company website and MSDS records.
- Handle all financial aspects (i.e., Accounts Payables, Accounts Receivables)
 of the business including inventory, budgets, payroll services, deposits, and
 taxation/licensing requirements.
- Create invoices, work orders and estimates. Order applicable parts and manage any customer concerns as needed.
- Scan vehicle computer modules for any current/historical codes and program/reflash vehicle modules using aftermarket J-2534 equipment.

ADVANCEMENT ASSISTANT

W.M. Keck Observatory / Kamuela, HI / 2016 - 2017

- Assist the Major Gifts Officer with processing all incoming donations.
- Maintain 'Raisers Edge' database of donor information and support the cultivation of donor relations.
- Plan and coordinate summit tours and dinner events for donors.

TECHNICAL STRESS ANALYST

The Boeing Company / Everett, WA / 2012 - 2016

- Assist in performing complex structural stress analysis for the 787 model interior commodities.
- Primary focal for the Flight Deck Seats analysis, Lean+/5S activities, and the 787-10 minor model which included developing process improvements, coordinating data transmittals, adhering to schedules, and interfacing with internal groups, partners, and suppliers.
- Responsible for prioritizing the entire 787 interior stress team's work statement, tracking all team metrics, reporting to senior leadership, programming macros to streamline repetitive team tasks, and creating other tools to productivity.
- Provide certification plan inputs and coordinate with the Federal Aviation Administration Authorized Representatives and engineers to certify the installation of the interiors for each unique customer configuration.